Dracula前情提要
Previously on Dracula...
Shaw将军是无辜的
General Shaw is innocent.
不是我毁了他  是你
I didn't destroy the man. You did.
Jonathan不在这
Jonathan's not here.
我相信如果你要
I'm sure you'll have no
重新找一个舞伴并不是什么难事
trouble finding another partner to dance with.
我爱你 Mina
I love you, Mina.
呃... 你该走了
Ehm... you need to leave.
该有人教教她什么是痛苦
Someone should teach her such pain.
我会教你怎么捕获Jonathan的心
I will teach you how to haunt Jonathan's dreams.
我进行了实验
I conducted an experiment
把这种物质
by adding this substance
注入人类面颊的细胞
to human cheek cells,
而那些死亡细胞复活了
and the dead cells reanimated.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
这台机器危害了公共安全
this machine is a threat to public safety.
恶龙会烧死了我的妻儿
The Order burnt my wife and children.
他们粉身碎骨之时
You will have your revenge.
也就是你我报仇雪恨之时
When we crush them, we both will.
用你的血清
With your serum,
我可以在阳光下行走
I can walk in the sun.
但是仅限于四个小时之内
But it will only allow you four hours in daylight.
- 其他人会怎么说? - 什么人?
- What would people say? - What people?
你的手在抖
Your hands are trembling.
你究竟爱谁 Alexander Grayson?
So who do you love most, Alexander Grayson?
不!
No!
先生 能问个问题么?
Sir, may I ask a question?
如果我告诉你不能
If I told you no,
你会不问么?
would it stop you?
应该不会
Probably not.
你打算在这里坐多久?
How long do you intend to sit here?
- 先生... - 我允许提问
- Sir... - I allowed a question.
但不代表我会回答
That does not mean I wish to answer it.
有种愚蠢叫做痴迷
There is folly in this obsession.
愚蠢且致命
Folly and threat.
如果你想要一个女孩
If you want the girl,
那就去争夺
then take her.
但如果你不能拥有
But if you cannot have her,
就放手
then walk away.
够了
Enough.
"争夺她  或放她走"
"Take her, or walk away."
若真有如此简单
If only it was that easy.
前者会把Mina置于危险之中
The first would put Mina in mortal danger.
至于后者...
But the second...
会让我生不如死
That would be the end of me.
爸爸 你在这做什么?
Father. What are you doing here?
我来接你回家
I've come to grab you away.
我从不工作到这么晚
I don't work this late
而且我才是个医师
and I actually am a physician.
我只是...我有些东西要...
I just... I have a few more things that I...
躲在这里 躲着我
Hiding here, avoiding me,
躲着Jonathan
avoiding Jonathan.
我没有躲着任何人
I'm not avoiding anyone.
不 不 让我说完
No, no. Let me speak.
那个美国人对你来说是什么?
What is the American to you?
我爱Jonathan
I love Jonathan.
我们从小青梅竹马 而且...
I have known him my entire life, and...
他就像我的一个家人
Well, he's like family to me.
他会成为我的丈夫
He will be my husband,
而我会成为他的妻子
and I will be his wife.
但是 告诉我 Mina
But, tell me, Mina.
但是Alexander...
But Alexander...
他身上散发着一种...
He exerts a kind of...
磁铁般的引力
Magnetic force.
不论我多么努力的尝试
And no matter how hard I try,
我都不能...
I can't...
听起来我就像一个傻瓜
I sound like a fool.
不 不是这样的
No, not at all.
我过去的生命中
I loved one woman
也爱过一个女人
in my life.
但是我和你母亲之间
But my path to your mother
也是起起伏伏
was hardly a straight line.
所以我做了
So I did the only possible thing
唯一能得到幸福的抉择
when it comes to happiness.
随心之所向
I followed my heart.
黑荒原 船头
Blackheath, bow,
Islington 还有Chelsea
Islington, and Chelsea.
四个  昨天晚上
Four. Tracked
已经全部被消灭
and exterminated this last evening.
感谢上帝
Good God.
我们可以得出一个不容置疑的论断
We can only draw one inescapable conclusion.
你如何否认?
How can you deny it?
所有的现象都很明显
The signs are clear.
伦敦现在有另一个年长的吸血鬼
There is another elder vampire in London.
但是你说过
But you said
你已经杀死了年长的吸血鬼
you'd killed the old one.
是的 但是祸患还在继续
I did. But the plague continues.
当年长的吸血鬼死去
Where the old one goes,
那么他的血裔也会相继死去
the sons and daughters follow.
所以这里还有一个
There is another one.
那就去吧
Then go.
找到他 干掉他
Find it and destroy it.
美好的夜晚 对吧?
Lovely night, ain't it?
从现在才开始
It is now.
第一次吧 从你的脸上看得出来
First time, by the looks of you.
- 怎么看出来的? - 别担心...
- How can you tell? - Not to worry...
Ladybird会照顾好每件事的
Ladybird'll take care of everything.
哦! 见鬼!
Oh! Bloody hell!
所以流言是真的
So the rumors are true.
真有一个猎人
A proper huntsman.
还是一个女人
And a woman, too.
是时候去死了
It's time to die.
太晚了 已经 死过了
Too late. Already dead.
啊!
Aah!
谁召你来的
Who called you?
- 我们的主人 - 名字
- Our master. - Name.
- 他有很多 - 我不喜欢猜谜
- He has many. - I'm not a fan of riddles.
- 名字 - 他会杀了我的
- Name. - He will destroy me.
- 名字 - 堕落者
- Name. - The Fell One.
骗子
Liar.
Vlad Tepes 穿刺者
Vlad Tepes. Vlad the Impaler.
Dracula
Dracula.
- 不可能 - 我们誓死效忠于他
- It cannot be. - We swarm to do his bidding.
万众齐心 我们就会制造出
Together, we will make
永无止境的黑暗
an endless night.
他的巢穴在哪?
Where's his nest?
告诉我!
Tell me!
我什么都会告诉你的
I'll tell you everything.
翻译：格  三文鱼
翻译  校对：老马
校对  监制：幸福ing形式
德  古  拉
第一季第八集
真 爱 字 幕 组
——— 出 品 ———
- 我有麻烦了 - 什么麻烦?
- I'm in trouble. - What kind of trouble?
发誓这事不会有第三个人知道
Swear to me this stays between us.
我发誓不会告诉任何人
I swear I will tell no one.
关于Shaw的事情
The story about Shaw
是彻头彻尾的谎言
was a complete fabrication.
那么那些证据呢?
What about the evidence?
他的财务记录...
His financial records...
假的 一丝一毫都是假的
Faked. Every shred of it.
你为什么这么做?
Why would you do such a thing?
我没有
I didn't.
我没有 是Grayson
I didn't. It was Grayson.
他策划了整件事情
He engineered the whole thing.
那就撤出来
So retract it.
我不能  Grayson把自己
I can't. Grayson was too clever
撇的一干二净
to get his hands dirty.
一定有什么人能证实
There must be someone
你所说的一切
who can corroborate your story.
- 那个会计? - 她不见了
- The bookkeeper? - She's gone.
她就凭空消失了
She's disappeared into thin air.
没人再在白天见过她
No one's seen her in days.
你觉得Grayson可能会...
You think Grayson might have...
你懂的...
You know...
- 什么?  - 让她消失?
- What? - Made her disappear?
是的
Yes.
你觉得你现在有危险了么?
Do you think you're in danger?
是的
Yes, I do.
那么这样
Then here.
拿着  你可能会用到的
Take this. You may need it.
你做的太过了
You've outdone yourself.
我从没想到过
I never thought
你会愚蠢到去屠杀
you'd be stupid enough to slaughter
苏格兰的警察总督
Chief Inspector of Scotland Yard.
我想找到真相  而且找到了
I wanted the truth and I got it.
是的  这我确信
Yes, I'm certain you did.
他告诉了我整个的阴谋
He told me the entire plot.
他们给所有人都下了毒
They poisoned all those people.
这是恶龙会
It's the Order of the Dragon.
你有什么好意外的?
It surprises you?
这证明我们的技术
It proves our technology
和此毫无关系
had nothing to do with it.
那又怎样
It doesn't matter.
恶龙会会使我们的共振器
The Order made it look like
看起来就是有问题
it was our resonator.
在大众的眼里
In the public's eye,
它是不安全的  致命的
it is unsafe, deadly.
那就会是他们唯一记得的事情
That is all they know and all they will remember.
即使机器被证实是无可非议的
Even if the technology is proven blameless.
都结束了  我们完了
It's finished. We are ruined.
那你觉得我们该怎么办?
And what do you suggest we do about it?
放弃?
Give up?
在我们辛苦做了这么多以后?
After all our hard work?
不  我不会放弃
No, I'm not giving up.
我会去复仇
I will have my revenge.
你会报仇雪恨的 当我...
You will have your revenge when I...
准备好了?
Ready?
你在说什么?
What were you saying?
你说我们去证明
You were saying we will prove
机器是无害的
the technology is harmless
然后继续原来的计划
and continue as planned.
是的
Yes.
Dracula是一个传说
Dracula is a myth.
是吓唬不听话的孩子的故事
A tale told to frighten children.
你已经失去理智了么?
Have you taken leave of your senses?
你们两个安静
Be quiet, both of you.
你相信我  是吗?
You believe me, don't you?
他曾是一个人类
He was a man.
他的名字是Vlad Tepes  穿刺者
His name was Vlad Tepes, Vlad the Impaler.
是中世纪的战士王子
He was a medieval warrior
以野蛮残酷而闻名
prince renowned for his savagery and ruthlessness.
曾是他的地区的首席猎人
He was master huntsman in his native land,
而且他曾效命于
and he served on the High Council
这个组织的高级委员会
of this very organization.
- 这太荒唐了  - 真荒谬
- This is absurd. - It's ridiculous.
她是对的  是有过这样一个人
She's right. There was such a man.
有关他的文字记载都被禁涉
The texts concerning him are forbidden to all
但是龙之会的领导人
but the Dragon's heads
和首席猎人知晓
and their chief huntsmen.
他无视龙之会
He defied the Ordo Draco,
被逐出了教会
was excommunicated by the Church
被判为有罪的异端
and found guilty of heresy.
他罪大恶极以至于
So grievous was his sin that
死刑已经不够作为刑罚
a sentence of death was considered inadequate.
所以他们举行神秘的仪式
So they employed occult rituals and transformed him
把他转化为永生的恶魔
into the living demon that we now know
也就是我们都知道的堕落者
as the Fell One,
Nosferatu  吸血鬼始祖
Nosferatu, primo Master vampire,
Dracula
Dracula.
不是被转化的
Created, not sired,
是我们创造的
by us.
你有什么证据证明
What proof do you have that
他在伦敦?
he's in London?
他毁掉我的先知
He swatted off my seers
就如同踩死蝼蚁一般
like flies.
他轻易就打败了Kruger
He easily bested Kruger,
在我麾下的
one of the most formidable huntsmen
最强大的猎人之一
I've ever had under my command.
他能躲避侦查
He's avoided detection.
他和那些听命于他的血裔
He's infested London
在为祸伦敦
with creatures answering his call,
但是最终  昨晚
and finally, last night,
其中一个已明确的说出他的名字
one of them explicitly named him.
那我估计他在委员会面前也会说的
And I presume it would do the same before the Council.
是的  她应该会
Well, she would.
前提是她没有被我的枪爆头
Had she not taken my weapon and blown her own head off.
多么巧合
How very convenient.
他是对的
He's right, of course.
你的猜想也许是真的  但是
Your suspicions may be true, but we cannot
我们不能仅凭一个
rely on the word
那种东西的一面之词
of one of those creatures.
我们需要证据  如山的铁证
Bring us proof. Compelling proof.
这是唯一能让这种说法
It's the only way such a claim
使人信服的方式
can be believed.
如果Dracula真在伦敦
If Dracula's in London,
先生  我一定会找到他
sir, I will find him.
我会一次解决掉他们
I will end him once and for all.
Jonathan
Jonathan.
你同意...
You agree...
我们之间不该有秘密的对吧?
That there should be no secrets between us?
是
Yes.
是Grayson
It's Grayson.
他怎么了?
What about him?
他当着我的面说谎
He lied to my face,
就为了破坏
in order to destroy
Shaw将军的名誉
the reputation of General Shaw.
但是Jonathan  你说过...
But Jonathan, you said that...
拜托  Mina
Please, Mina.
请你听我说完
Just please, listen to me.
Grayson勒索了Laurent勋爵
Grayson blackmailed Lord Laurent,
现在Laurent就死了
and now Laurent's dead,
就像还年轻的Davenport一样
as is young Davenport,
都是他搞出来的
and by his own hand.
但是报纸不是这样说的
That's not what the papers said.
他会不惜一切手段
He will do anything
去建成他的项目
in the pursuit of his grand project.
勒索  诽谤...
Blackmail, slander...
据我所知  还有谋杀
And for all I know, murder.
谋杀?
Murder?
他是我见过的最邪恶的人
He's the closest thing to evil I've ever seen.
Jonathan...
- Mina...  - 如果这是真的...
- Mina... - If this is true...
那你为什么还要继续为他效力呢?
Then why do you continue in his employ?
我有我的理由
I have my reasons.
- 而且是好理由  - 没有秘密
- And good ones. - No secrets.
求你 给我点时间
Please, just give me time,
我会解释所有事情
and I will explain everything to you.
但是在那之前...
But until then...
那之前
Until then,
你一定要远离Alexander Grayson
you stay away from Alexander Grayson.
- 我想见她  Jenkins
- I want to see her, Jenkins,
让我进去
let me in.
Jayne女士外出了 先生
Lady Jayne is traveling, sir.
我知道她在这  让我进去
I know she's here. Let me in.
Jenkins  让他进来
Jenkins, let him in, please.
Alexander  你的突然到来
Alexander, how lovely of you
多让人开心
to drop by.
谢谢  Jenkins  没事了
Thank you, Jenkins, that will be all.
如果你需要我
If you need me,
- 随时叫我  - 好的
- just call. - I will.
抱歉
Excuse me,
我不记得有邀请你
I don't remember inviting you in.
我们从没正式见过面吧？
We've never stood on formality, have we?
你在这干什么  Alexander？
Why are you here, Alexander?
- 你知道为什么  - 嗯  我知道
- You know why. - Yes, yes I do.
好吧你赢了
You win.
我不明白
I don't understand.
一切都结束了  Alexander
It's over, Alexander.
我会承认的
I'll admit it,
我已经看到了我的结果
I have met my match.
你是想听这个吗？
Is that what you want to hear?
你打败我了
You have bested me.
现在  请出去
Now, please, just go.
我已经没有时间继续玩这个游戏了
I'm far too busy to continue playing this game.
游戏？
Game?
得了吧  收手吧好吗
Oh, please, just stop.
我用我的生命来保护你
I risked my life to protect yours.
是  没错
Yes, you did.
而且我无论如何也搞不明白
And for the life of me, I can't work out why.
你的竟然芳心他许了
Your heart clearly belongs to another.
你什么时候知道的？
When did you know?
自从你跟她…
When you danced with her...
在她订婚舞会上一起跳舞
At her engagement party.
有那么明显吗？
Was it that obvious?
对我来说  太明显不过了
To me, glaringly so.
Grayson先生
Mr. Grayson...
总是Mina  对么
It was always Mina,
你什么时候跟我在一起过？
wasn't it, when you were with me?
不
No.
你说谎
You're lying.
所以  你想告诉我点什么呢？
So, what have you got to tell me?
我找到了一些人
I found some men.
嗯
Mm-mmm.
这些人  可靠吗？
These men, are they reliable?
嗯  非常可靠  是的
Mm-mmm, very much so, yes.
- 开个价吧  - 好
- For a price. - Good.
现在你要做的就是介绍一下他们
Now all you need to do is introduce them
给这个充满疑问的女士
to the lady in question.
那么我得多久之后再介绍呢？
And how soon will I start making these introductions?
越快越好
The sooner the better.
我要杀哪只？
Who do I have to kill?
不如别杀了吧  先生？
May I suggest no one, sir?
也许只有这一次呢
Perhaps just this once.
如果真相不会大白的话
If the truth won't set the resonator free,
也许有人要继续牺牲了
perhaps someone's excised heart will.
我有那些当官的名单
I have the name of a bureaucrat
为了健康  我确信
on the Board of Health, who I am assured
我能接受适度的自由
will be most accommodating for a very modest fee.
好的  贿赂那些蛀虫吧
Fine, bribe the worm.
如果必须的话
A king's ransom,
一个国王的赎金
if you must.
但是如果不成功的话
But if it doesn't succeed,
我们就按照我的方法来
then we do it my way.
明白了
Understood.
那个  抱歉
Sorry, um,
男管家让我进来的
the butler let me in.
Murray小姐  真的好巧啊
Miss Murray, what a pleasant surprise.
Renfield
Renfield.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
我跟Jonathan谈过话了
I've spoken with Jonathan.
他看起来很不安
He seemed quite terrified.
- 为什么？  - 因为你
- By what? - By you.
真荒谬
That's preposterous.
- 是么？  - 当然了
- Is it? - Of course.
你跟Jonathan一样了解我
You know me as long as Jonathan has.
- 我让你不安了吗？  - 没有…
- Do I terrify you? - No...
但是我一点都不了解你
But I don't know you as well.
恰恰相反  Murray小姐
On the contrary, Miss Murray,
我认为你比任何其他人
I would venture that you know me better
都要了解我
than anyone else.
请原谅我
Forgive me.
我经常
I sometimes give voice to things
言常人所不敢言
that are better left unsaid.
不要道歉了
No, don't apologize.
这是我最欣赏你的一点
It's what I like most about you.
美国人  你的真诚
Americans. Your honesty.
我永远不会对你撒谎
I will never lie to you.
我保证
You have my word.
为什么Jonathan那么不安？
Why was Jonathan so upset?
Mina  有个很有权势的人
Mina, there are powerful men
希望阻止我
who wish to stop me,
但是实际上  我必须去与
but on occasion, I have to match
他们的无情竞争
their ruthlessness,
不然的话未来将一片黯淡
or the future will be lost.
不要犯错误了  Mina
Make no mistake, Mina,
Harker现在的无情跟我有一比了
Harker's proving to be as ruthless as I am.
事实上  比你更甚
On occasion, more so.
- 不  你错了  - 有么？
- No, you're wrong. - Am I?
Jonathan是对的
Jonathan was right.
你感染了人们
You infect people.
你称之为魅力
You call it charm,
但这些都只是你为了自己的私利
but it's all for your own self-interest.
Jonathan和我不会再被你所用了
Jonathan and I will not be used up by you.
一个标准的英国绅士应该
A proper English gentleman must have
在婚礼上有个完整的英国背心
a proper English waistcoat on his wedding day,
但是首先
but first,
他必须要有个合适的衣服
one must select the appropriate fabric.
我有调色板
I have swatches.
Lucy  我觉得这个调色非常重要
Lucy, I'm sure the swatches are very important,
但是我真的不能耽误工作  所以…
but I really can't be late for work, so...
我一点也不关心什么狗屁的调色…
I don't care a damn about the swatches...
为什么  你会在这
Then why... why are you here,
如果不是调色板的事的话？
if not for the swatches?
你会觉得我是个傻瓜
You'll think me a fool.
Lucy…
Lucy...
我来着是因为我一直在想你
I came here because I can't get you out of my mind.
我一直拘束着我的情感
I keep my feelings close.
一直以来都是这样
I always have.
太多  以至于你完全没有
So much so, you seem entirely
察觉到他们
unaware of them.
你这样多久…
How long have you...
你什么时候开始……
when did you...
我没预见到这个也没有计划过
I neither planned nor expected this,
但是  我们现在在这
and yet, here we are.
你和我
You and me.
Lucy…
Lucy...
不管是什么  最终都会过去的
Whatever this is, it will pass.
是的  如果仅仅是看着Mina的份上的话
It must, if only for Mina's sake. Mina,
我们都爱着她
whom we both love.
你说的对  当然
You're right, of course.
我只希望我能得到你的力量
I only wish I had your strength of character.
我们不说这个了好吗
Let's not speak of this again,
看在Mina的份上
for Mina's sake.
是的  这只是行动的一部分
Yes, that is the only course of action,
我完全同意
I completely agree.
一个决定
One condition.
当然
Of course.
给我个吻帮我度过这个难关
A kiss to help me after.
不  不要  这是不可能的
No, no, that's... that's impossible.
承认我的安慰吧
Do not deny me this consolation.
对于我遭受的痛苦来说
It's a small crumb to
这只是很小的一部分
ease the pain of all that I shall never have.
一个吻而已
One kiss.
朋友之间的一个吻
A kiss between friends.
你人很好  你也很慷慨
You're kind. And you're generous.
不不不不
No, no, no, no.
我不能不遵守对Mina的约定
I cannot break my promise to Mina.
Mina
Mina.
你俩是该有多高兴啊
How happy you both must be.
总是在一起
Always together,
就算是你在庄园工作的时候
even when you're working at Carfax Manor,
她也经常拜访你
she's always visiting you.
你在说什么啊？
What are you talking about?
我昨天见她了
I saw her there yesterday,
上个星期也是
last week as well.
她都形成习惯了
She does make a habit of it.
她因为你才去拜访的  不是吗？
It was you she was visiting, wasn't it?
Mina Murray在审判我！
Mina Murray judges me!
她嘲笑我！
She scorns me!
她从来没有原谅过我！
She will not forgive me!
我需要点血
I want some blood.
不
No.
我不能让你离开这个庄园
I can't let you leave Carfax Manor,
不能这么出去
not like this.
- 谁能挡我？  - 我能
- Who will stop me? - I will.
我要血！
I want blood!
Renfield  看在你自己的份上
Renfield, for your own sake.
Mina Murray已经扎根在你心里了
Mina Murray's taken root in you.
她的存在
Her existence
只能使你的本性难以抑制
only makes your true nature harder to disguise.
她让你开始讨厌自己的本质--Dracula
She makes you hate the one thing you are - Dracula.
但是要不是Dracula
But without Dracula,
你永远不可能打败恶龙会
you can never defeat the Ordo Draco.
我到底该怎么做？
What am I supposed to do?
忘了她或者得到她
Forget her or take her.
我告诉你离他远一点
I told you to stay away from him.
是的我知道
Yes, I know,
但是我只是试着寻找真相
but I was only trying to uncover the truth.
我来告诉你事实
I told you the truth.
是  当然  但是我想知道…
Yes, of course, but I wanted to know...
你觉得Grayson的话比我的可靠？
And you take Grayson's word over mine?
没有
No.
这一段时间  我装作没看见
This whole time, I tried not to see it,
但是现在就发生在我眼前
and it was right in front of me.
看见什么？
See what?
- 你和Grayson  - 你怎么敢
- You and Grayson. - How dare you.
我去那是去保护你
I went there to protect you,
而你却做最坏的猜想
and you assume the worst.
之前呢？
And the time before?
有幅照片
There was a phonograph,
在医院跳舞时候照的
for the dance at the hospital.
- 总是有理由
- There's always a reason,
是吧？  - 是  很好的理由
isn't there? - Yes, a very good reason.
或者是你故意让它们发生的
Or do you just invent them,
所以你就有理由去见他了
so you have an excuse to see him,
跟他去调情？
to flirt with him?
不  我从来没有
No, I would never even...
我不相信你！
I don't believe you!
我不相信
I don't.
最后一次问你
For the last time,
为什么跟自己
why must you make this
这么过不去呢？
so difficult for yourselves?
他在哪？
Where is he?
这是圣水
It's holy water.
- 你渴么？  - 你问啥  我说啥
- Are you thirsty? - If you ask, I'll answer.
- Dracula在哪？  - 我不知道
- Where is Dracula? - I don't know.
没人看见过他
No one sees him.
他们说他能在白天出没
And they say he lives in the light.
那是不可能的
That's impossible.
我听到的就是这个
It's what I hear.
他不需要夜幕的遮掩了
He has no need for the blanket of night.
对他来说  太阳
For him, the sun
是另外一个星星而已
is just another star.
离得远近  没有任何区别
Close or far away, it makes no difference.
他超越了上帝
He has bested God.
怎么超越的？
How?
跟如何有关系吗？
What does it matter how?
事实就是这样的
It is.
你会因他的愤怒而害怕
You will fear his wrath by day,
无论白天还是黑夜
by night,
而且你永远不会看见他的到来
and you will never see him coming.
15年小心翼翼的计划
15 years of meticulous planning,
用大量财富发展起来的技术
A fortune developing a technology
去破坏他们的石油利润
to undermine their petroleum interests,
使其浪费
wasted.
- 我们还有选择  - 选择？
- We still have options. - Options?
教授  你真的应该
Professor, you really
坐下来然后冷静一下
should take a seat and try to calm yourself.
告诉我你已经跟那些官僚
Tell me you've made some progress
取得进展了
with these bureaucrats?
我们所有的关系
Every contact
都将我们的预算视而不见
we've had has ignored our advances.
这就像我们被冻结
It's as if we've been frozen out
然后从顶上摔下来
from the top down.
- 这个人  Browning…  - Browning？
- This man, Browning... - Browning?
是啊  看起来他运用了
Yes, he seems to exert an
铁腕手段控制了伦敦的政治集团
iron grip over London's political machine.
他在Grayson先生的黑名单里面
He's on Mr. Grayson's short list.
最高委员会
Definitely High Council.
他也许就是恶龙会的首领
He may even be the Dragon's Head.
不！
No!
爸爸  爸爸  爸爸  爸爸！
Papa, papa, papa, papa!
不！
No!
你知道他吗？
Do you know of him?
不  我从未听说过这个男人
No, I've never heard of this man.
有人吗？
Hello?
你想干什么？
What do you want?
你在这干什么？
What are you doing here?
你好啊  Murray小姐
Hello, Miss Murray.
多美好的夜晚啊  是不是？
Quite a lovely night, isn't it?
啊  呃…
Ah, uh...
- 现在  现在  - 啊！
- Now, now. - Aah!
我喜欢有勇气的女孩
I like a girl with spirit...
但只是点到为止
But only to a point.
现在  我保证你没见过
Now, I'm assuming that you've never seen
硫酸滴在人脸上是什么样子的
what sulfuric acid does to a body's face.
它直接穿过皮肤  就像…
It eats right through the skin, just like...
火穿过纸一样
Fire through paper.
嘴唇和眼睑…
Lips and lids...
烧掉
Burn right off.
把鼻子变成两个洞洞
Turns the nose into nothing but a couple of holes.
看好了学着点  先生们
Watch and learn, gents.
看准了好好学
Watch and learn.
弗拉德三世
Vlad the Impaler.
德古拉
Dracula.
她受的大部分是皮外伤
Her injuries are largely superficial.
她会好起来的  Jonathan
She will be fine, Jonathan.
- 谁会做这种事？  - 我不知道
- Who could have done this? - I don't know.
她会恢复吗？
Will she recover?
她会的
She will survive.
医生
Doctor.
Mina
Mina.
谁做的？
Who did this?
Mina
Mina.
这很重要
It's important.
你一定要告诉我们一切
You must tell us everything.
有仨男人...
There were three men...
他们袭击了我
And they attacked me
并把我按在了桌子上。
and held me on the table.
太快了  我记不住了
It was so fast. I can't... I can't remember.
谁？  是谁做的？
Who? Who did this?
他拿着一个瓶子
He had a bottle.
- 一瓶硫酸  - 额  天那。
- A bottle of acid. - Oh, my God.
他有一块胎记
And a birthmark,
他的脸上有块焰色记
a port wine stain on his face.
- 额  天那  - 谁啊？
- Oh, my God. - What is it?
- 是警察  - 什么...？
- The police. - Yes...?
必须马上通知他们
They must be informed immediately.
Jonathan...
- Harker！- 你要干什么？
- Harker! - What do you want?
我和你一样  公平
I want the same thing you do, justice.
我不需要你的帮助
I don't need your help.
是  你不要
No, you don't.
那个有胎记的男人
The man with the birthmark,
他叫Hackett
his name is Hackett.
Hackett是Davenport的人
Hackett's Davenport's man.
我必须警告有关当局
I must alert the proper authorities.
警告他们？
Alert them?
- 是的  - 真的吗？
- Yes. - Really?
你要告诉他们Davenport勋爵
You're gonna tell them Lord Davenport
让他的手下
sent his man
用硫酸袭击你的未婚妻？
to attack your fiancee with acid?
是的。
Yes.
他是一位集财富和声誉的
He is a well-respected man
备受敬仰的人
of wealth and reputation.
警察往往对那样的人从轻处理
Police tend to treat men like that lightly.
- 他们一定知道真相  - 真相？
- They must know the truth. - The truth?
这是你的观点
It's your word,
一个前新闻工作者
an ex-journalist,
和一个上议院的贵族对抗
against a peer of the realm.
好吧  你觉得他们会相信谁呢？
Come on. Who do you think they're going to believe?
好的  我会亲自问他的
Well, then I'll ask him myself.
Davenport是不会骗我的
Davenport won't lie to me.
我不会在乎他有多少钱
I don't care how much money he has,
我会让他开口的
I'll make him answer.
额  Harker先生
Ah, Mr. Harker.
请告诉我真相
Tell me the truth.
实在抱歉  我还不知道
Sorry, I haven't an earthly idea
你们在说什么
what you're talking about.
你的人  Hackett
Your man, Hackett.
他袭击了Mina
He attacked Mina.
这是对Shaw将军的报复
This was retaliation for General Shaw.
你怎么对一个无辜的女人
How dare you go after
下此毒手？
an innocent woman?
听着  小男孩
Listen, dear boy,
我什么都不知道
I don't know anything about this.
Murray小姐  她还好么？
Miss Murray, is she all right?
谁送你来的？
Who sent you here?
没人
No one.
不  是Grayson  是不？
No. It was Grayson, wasn't it?
他把这种思想灌输到你脑袋里的么？
He put the ideas into your head?
唆使你来我这的么？
Goaded you into confronting me?
你冤枉我了
You're pointing the gun at the wrong man.
难道你看不出他的目的么？
Can't you see what he's up to?
不论怎样  他赢了  明白了么？
Either way, he wins. See?
不管是你杀了我去坐牢
Whether you kill me and go to jail,
还是我用枪把你当作入侵者杀死
or I get a gun and kill you as an intruder,
他还是赢了
he still wins.
赢什么了？  你在说些什么？
Wins what? What are you talking about?
想想！  最终谁会留下来
Think! Who will be left behind
照顾Murray小姐？
to look after Miss Murray?
在内心深处  你是知道的。
You see, deep down, you know that's true.
你看见过他们在一块
You've seen them together.
他们看向彼此的眼神
You've seen the way they look at one another.
他喜欢她  并且她…
He adores her. And she...
那是个天大的笑话！
That's a damn lie!
我可以证明给你看
I can prove it to you.
我指给你看  小心
Let me show you. Careful,
那个左轮手枪…可能走火
that revolver... it could go off.
请告诉我真相
Then tell me the truth.
他们背叛你了
They've betrayed you.
最近
See, recently,
我发现Grayson一直在找
I discovered that Grayson has been searching
一幅画
for one particular painting.
十年了  他一直在找
For 10 years, he's been looking,
遍布欧洲的每一次拍卖会
in every auction and every gallery
和每一个画廊
across Europe.
- 停  - 最终他找到了
- Stop. - And then he found it.
我知道是因为我从他那把画偷来了
I know this because I stole it from him.
- 不要动  - 你自己看
- Don't move. - You'll see for yourself.
他的痴迷远远超出了染料和画布
His obsession goes far beyond mere paint and canvas.
他雇佣你是为了能靠近她
He hires you so that he can get closer to her.
他甚至在他自己家举办你的婚礼
He even hosts your engagement party at his own home.
- 闭嘴  - 求你了  不要…  这是真的  听着
- Shut up. - Please, no... it's true. Listen.
我给你看   然后你就会明白了
Let me show you, and then you'll see.
然后你就什么都知道了
Then you'll understand everything.
额  天哪  不
Oh, God, no.
Davenport  Davenport…
Davenport, Davenport...
那边那个
You there.
你需要帮助么？
You need help?
你赶紧走
Best be on your way now.
那再见了
Cheerio, then.
Jonathan
Jonathan.
是什么风把你…？
What in the world are you...?
有人么
Hello.
亲爱的  你一定累坏了吧
Darling, you must be exhausted.
希望你还没吃饭呢
I hope you haven't eaten.
厨子为你温着晚餐呢
The cook's kept dinner warm for you.
谢谢  亲爱的
Thank you, my dear.
今天过的怎么样啊？
How was your day?
你不会相信的
You won't believe it,
我有了确实的证据…
but I have it on good authority that Lady...
- 我的天那  夫人
- What in God's Name, Mrs.
Gulliver？- 孩子们  孩子们…
Gulliver? - The children, the children...
他们不见了  他们不见了…
They're gone, they're gone...
额  天哪…
Oh, my God...
先生  女士们  有个人带他们进来了
Sir, ma'am, a man took them in.
不！
No!
你让我告诉你真相…
You asked me to tell you the truth...
给我保证
Made me promise.
我现在就告诉你
I'll tell it to you now.
自从我初次见你一切都改变了
Nothing has been the same since first I saw you.
你是我无法理解的神奇
You're a magic beyond my understanding.
我知道这是不可能的
I know it's impossible,
但是你是Ilona  回到我身边
but you are Ilona, come back to me.
但是你不止如此
But you're more than that.
你也是Mina
You are Mina too.
现在  我一直隐蔽自己的感情…
Now, I've tried to keep my feelings close...
但是我做不到
But I cannot.
你已超越我的能力范围
You make me want more than I could possibly have.
你想让我在阳光下漫步
You make me want to walk in the sun.
我属于你
I belong to you.
而且你属于我
And you belong to me.
Davenport勋爵死了
Lord Davenport is dead.
Harker先生像你吩咐的那样做了
Mr. Harker worked out just as you planned.